973-735-7140 nicom917@gmail.com ncmitran@svr.edu

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Pursuing a major in Information Management and Technology at the iSchool of Syracuse University. Effectively mastered time-management in the workplace, and have before demonstrated courtesy and patience when dealing with clients. Versed in a professional level of customer service, which has reinforced my interpersonal and problem resolution skills in time sensitive situations. Pursuing an internship in an IT oriented discipline to further enrich my already completed coursework with real workplace experiences

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Syracuse University, Syracuse, New York

Pursuing a degree in Information Management & Technology, Jun. 2018 - Jun. 2023

#### Information Technology Coursework

- IST 442 Agile Project Management Methodology
- IST 233 Intro to Computer Networking
- IST 344 Information Reporting & Presentation
- IST 345 Managing Info Systems Projects
- IST 346 Information TechManagement & Administration
- IST 352 Information Analysis of Organizational Systems
- IST 359 Intro to Database Management Systems
- IST 425 Enterprise Risk Management
- IST 263 Intro to Front-End Web Development/HTML
- IST 256 Applied Programming For Information Systems
- Effectively managed multiple responsibilities and demands using problem solving and time management skills
- Employed a wide variety of team management and interpersonal skills to navigate through complex issues in a group environment
- Demonstrated a willingness to adapt, commit, and overcome to foreign challenges in unfamiliar environments

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### IT Consultant, Whitman School of Management. Syracuse, NY

Sep. 2021 - Current

- Demonstrated on-the-spot, tailored, applicable problem solving skills regarding a variety of different customer requests and issues
- Maintained, managed, and provided support for a diverse array of client tickets/requests and executed tailored solutions in real time
- Worked closely alongside a team of IT professionals to measure, plan, and assess different technical challenges and provide relevant solutions in a timely manner
- Schedule: Monday 12pm-4pm, Tuesday 12pm-4pm, Thursday 8am-2pm, Weekends variable hours

#### Customer Service Representative, Domino's. Cedar Grove, NJ

Jan. 2017 – Jan. 2018

- · Provide great communication and customer service to clients in person and over the phone to ameliorate a plethora of unique concerns
- Managed and communicated effectively with other team members in a fast paced kitchen environment that averages 80 orders an hour
- Demonstrate a high-level of time management under pressure while routinely switching to different tasks

#### Banquet Server, The Grove. Cedar Grove, NJ

Jun. 2018 - Sep. 2018

- Successfully plan, maintain, and deconstruct up to three different events over the course of 11-19 hour shifts for up to 400-500 guests
- Practiced a professional standard of patience, dedication, and overall professionalism when catering to guests specific wants and needs

# **VOLUNTEER WORK / PERSONAL ENDEAVORS**

# Camp Counselor, Camp New Day. Stroudsburg, PA

Aug. 2018 - Sep. 2018

- Responsible for leading and providing support to a variety of different developmentally disabled adults throughout their day
- · Guided campers by aiding with meals, getting dressed, time management, hygiene, activities, and any other challenges
- Facilitated problem resolution techniques with campers who were distressed or in conflict with other individuals

# Desktop Solutions Work / Experience, Self-Employed, Cedar Grove, NJ

Jul. 2015 - Jul. 2019

• Designed, constructed, and supported tailored desktop solutions for clients based on a wide array of personal needs

## ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE/SKILLS

- Microsoft Projects
- Microsoft Teams
- Microsoft Azure
- Tableau
- C++
- Python
- Microsoft Office 365 Suite

- Amazon Web Services
- Google Office Suite
- Google Cloud Services
- Teamviewer, Slack, Zoom, Skype
- Windows, Linux, Mac
- HTML
- SQL